Douglass Crockwell collection, 1897-1976, 1934-1968
George Eastman Museum
- Series 1, Documents, 1934-1976; undated
  - Subseries 1, Moving Images, 1934-1970; undated
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- misc. articles, 1948-1956; 1967; undated (Folder 11)
        Magazine articles, newspaper clippings, and book excerpts regarding Crockwell, experimental animation, Mutoscopes, the "Mutoscopes" exhibition at the Museum of Modern Art, and the International Mutoscope Reel Company. Includes a copy of Crockwell's essay "A Background to Free Animation" from Film Culture #32, a Cinema 16 catalog, and program notes from various film series and festivals featuring Crockwell's films.
  - Subseries 2, Commercial Illustration, 1966; undated
    Subseries consists of documents and photographs related to Crockwell's professional work as a commercial illustrator.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - [Christmas cards, gallery catalog], undated (Folder 12)
        Three Christmas cards, two featuring Crockwell's artwork.
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Photographs], 1966; undated (Folder 15)
        Black-and-white prints, negatives, and transparencies. Includes contact sheets featuring Crockwell's commercial paintings.
      - [Sketches], undated (Folder 16)
        Pencil, pen and ink, and charcoal sketches and related notes. Illustrations include sketch of a holiday sing-along, possibly for the painting used for the 1959 General Motors Christmas card; optical apparatuses, possibly including the Pan-Stereo Sweep camera system; designs for "Ila Keller Batik" and "Illustrations by Douglass Crockwell"; sketches of Pirithous battling Eurytion.
      - [Photographs], undated (Folder 19)
        Photographic prints, transparencies, and negatives. Includes several untitled reproductions of Crockwell's commercial illustrations.
  - Subseries 3, Personal and Civic Affairs, 1941-1976
    Subseries includes records related to Crockwell's personal life as well as his activities as a member of civic, municipal, and cultural organizations, mainly in Glens Falls, NY. Prominent are records produced during Crockwell's tenure as director of the Hyde Collection.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- Mutoscope collecting, 1963-1967; undated (Folder 1)
        Meeting notes regarding property value assessments.
      - Crockwell -- doodles & sketches, undated (Folder 2)
        Home construction sketches and cost estimates.
      - [Christmas cards, gallery catalog], undated (Folder 12)
        Biography of Charlotte Pruyn Hyde, owner of Hyde House.
      - [Envelope labeled: Hyde Collection misc.], 1952; 1964-1967 [bulk]; undated (Folder 13)
        Correspondence and documents related to the Hyde Collection and Glens Falls-area civic and community activities. Materials originally collected in a manila mailing envelope addressed to Crockwell and labeled "Hyde Coll. Misc."
      - [Financial notebook], 1946-1948 (Folder 14)
        Dated record of household employees' wages, withholdings, social security, and payment balances, along with other expenses.
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Correspondence, notes, will], 1941; 1951; 1958-1968; 1971; 1975-1976; undated (Folder 17)
        Personal and financial notes; professional, civic and personal correspondence; two letters from father Charles Roland Crockwell; meeting minutes from the Planning Board of the City of Glens Falls; correspondence regarding research on sculptor David Smith; Crockwell's last will and testament dated 1951, unsigned.
  - Subseries 4, Inventions, 1939-1968; undated
    Subseries includes correspondence, patent documents, drawings, and sketches related to Crockwell's inventions, mainly the wax-slicing and paint-on-glass apparatuses devised for the creation of animated films.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- doodles & sketches, undated (Folder 2)
        Designs for Mutoscopes and other machines (including sketch of a double lens/lamp film projector).
      - Crockwell -- self promoted efforts, 1944-1945; 1952; 1958-1968 (Folder 6)
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Sketches], undated (Folder 16)
        Pencil, pen and ink, and charcoal sketches and related notes. Sketches of optical apparatuses, possibly including the Pan-Stereo Sweep camera system.
      - Crockwell -- patent papers, 1939-1949; 1959; 1964; undated (Folder 18)
        Patent documents and other materials related to Crockwell's inventions, particularly the wax-slicing machine and the paint-on-glass apparatus. Documents also include letters related to patent applications, specifications, and amendments. Much of the correspondence is with patent attorney Charles H. Andros.
      - [Photographs], undated (Folder 19)
        Photographic prints, transparencies, and negatives. Includes a photograph of an Iron Horse Mutoscope alongside a machine of Crockwell's own design and two photos of what is possibly Crockwell's Pan-Stereo Sweep camera and viewer.
  - Subseries 5, Scientific Research, 1963-1967; undated
    Subseries comprises manuscripts, articles, and sketches related to Crockwell's interest in atomic physics and other sciences.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- Mutoscope collecting, 1963-1967; undated (Folder 1)
        Notes regarding gravitational and acceleration fields, and diagrams and notes for a "Machine for Inducing a Non-Symmetrical Gradient of the Inertial Field."
      - Crockwell -- doodles & sketches, undated (Folder 2)
        "Precession of Orbit" diagram.
  - Subseries 6, Biographical Information, 1966; undated
    Subseries consists of biographical sketches, curriculum vitae, obituaries, and timelines.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- biographical inc. obit., 1966; undated (Folder 5)
        Primary and secondary biographical source materials, including Who's Who in America entry, a circa 1948 biographical essay written by the United States Brewers Foundation, exhibition brochures, newspaper obituaries, curriculum vitae, and handwritten notes.
- Series 2, Photographs and Illustrations, ca. 1966; undated
  - Subseries 1, Photographs, ca. 1966; undated [bulk]
    Subseries includes photographic prints, 35mm transparencies, and black-and-white negatives related to Crockwell's personal life as well as his work as commercial illustrator, filmmaker, and inventor.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell --MoMA correspondence incl. photos, 1934-1944; 1959-1975; undated (Folder 4)
        One 8" x 10"Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) publicity photograph of "two new Mutoscopes, designed and loaned by Douglass Crockwell."
    - no title (Box C364a)
      - [Photographs from Crockwell's films], undated (Folder 1)
        Color frame enlargements from unidentified films printed on Mutoscope cards.
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Photographs], undated (Folder 19)
        Photographic prints, transparencies, and negatives. Photographs include frame enlargements from Glens Falls Sequence and The Long Bodies of various sizes; several untitled reproductions of Crockwell's commercial illustrations; an Iron Horse Mutoscope alongside a machine of Crockwell's own design; three small color photographs of abstract paintings; three small frame enlargements from the "Calvary" sequence of Glens Falls Sequence; two photos of what is possibly Crockwell's Pan-Stereo Sweep camera and viewer.
  - Subseries 2, Drawings, undated
    Subseries consists of pencil, pen and ink, and charcoal sketches by Crockwell, mostly related to his commercial artwork and inventions.
    - no title (Box C364)
      - Crockwell -- doodles & sketches, undated (Folder 2)
        Pen and pencil drawings including "Thumbprints by Douglass Crockwell" logo doodles; designs for Mutoscopes and other machines (including sketch of a double lens/lamp film projector); home construction sketches and cost estimates; "Precession of Orbit" diagram.
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Sketches], undated (Folder 16)
- Series 3, Moving Images, 1897-1968
  - Subseries 1, Films, ca. 1937; 1946
    Subseries includes work Crockwell produced on motion-picture film. Includes both positives and negatives. For information regarding access to these films please contact the Film Study Center at the George Eastman Museum (filmstudycenter@eastman.org).
    - [Fantasmagoria #1], undated
      16mm acetate positive (color archival element)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:2067
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      16mm acetate positive (black-and-white)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0458
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      16mm acetate positive (color original reversal)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0459
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      35mm acetate negative (color)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0460
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0466
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0468
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:0469
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      16mm polyester positive (color)
      Accession No.: 2002:0053:0001
    - Glens Falls Sequence, 1946
      Accession No.: 2003:0442:0001
    - Long Bodies, The, 1946
      35mm acetate positive (color)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:1235
    - Long Bodies, The, 1946
      16mm acetate positive (color)
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:1354
    - Long Bodies, The, 1946
      Accession No.: 1975:0007:1355
    - Long Bodies, The, 1946
      1984:2897:0001
    - Simple Destiny: An Abstract Phantasmagoria, 1937
      16mm acetate negative (black-and-white)
      1975:0007:2071
    - no title (Box C364-OS)
      - [Douglass Crockwell,Glens Falls Sequence segment, 50 frames, 16mm color reversal], undated (Folder 20)
        Five strips of acetate safety film mounted between two sheets of glass. No discernible edge code on film stock.
      - [Douglass Crockwell,Glens Falls Sequence segment, 60 frames, 16mm Kodachrome], undated (Folder 21)
        60 individual frames arranged in six columns of 10 numbered rows, mounted between two sheets of glass. The accompanying legal-sized envelope labeled "Remaining Pieces" and containing strips of 16mm film from the same sequence (some frames are numbered) was moved from its original location in Box 3 to its current location on 5/1/2015.
  - Subseries 2, Mutoscope Reels, 1897-1907; 1915; 1965; undated
    - Sub-subseries 1, Collected, 1897-1907; 1915; undated
      Sub-subseries includes commercially produced Mutoscope reels collected by Crockwell.
      - Subject 228:Dressing Room Scene, A, 1897 (Box Box 1)
        American Mutoscope and Biograph Company
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0001
      - Subject 238:Affair of Honor, An, 1897 (Box Box 2)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0002
      - Subject 694:Tramp and the Muscular Cook, The, 1898 (Box Box 3)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0003
      - Subject 881:'Moving' Picture, A, 1899 (Box Box 4)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0004
      - Subject 957:Reginald's First High Hat, 1899 (Box Box 5)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0005
      - Subject 1443:How the Old Maid Got a Husband, 1900 (Box Box 6)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0006
      - Subject 1527:Career of Crime. No. 5, A, 1900 (Box Box 7)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0007
      - Subject 1576:Trouble in Hogan's Alley, 1900 (Box Box 8)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0008
      - Subject 1671:Good Time Behind the Scenes, A, 1900 (Box Box 9)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0009
      - Subject 1874:Close Shave, A, 1901 (Box Box 10)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0010
      - Subject 2479:Fatal Attempt to Loop-the-loop on a Bicycle, A, 1903 (Box Box 11)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0011
      - Subject 2528:From Show Girl to Burlesque Queen, 1903 (Box Box 12)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0012
      - Subject 2714-B:Love and Jealousy Behind the Scenes, 1904 (Box Box 13)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0013
      - Subject 2944:Seashore Baby, The, 1904 (Box Box 14)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0014
      - Subject 3013:Al Treloar in Muscle Exercises, 1905 (Box Box 15)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0015
      - Subject 3060:Adjustable Chair, The, 1905 (Box Box 16)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0016
      - Subject 3072:Japanese-Russian Peace Envoys, 1905 (Box Box 17)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0017
      - Subject 3074-A:Bertha Claiche: The Lovers, 1905 (Box Box 18)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0018
      - Subject 3076:She Banked in Her Stocking; or, Robbed of Her All, 1905 (Box Box 19)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0019
      - Subject 3080:Teasing, 1905 (Box Box 20)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0020
      - Subject 3085-B:Horse-Thief, The, 1905 (Box Box 21)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0021
      - Subject 3104:Airy Fairy Lillian Tries on Her New Corsets, 1905 (Box Box 22)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0022
      - Subject 3099:Halloween, 1905 (Box Box 23)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0023
      - Subject 3118:Fight for a Bride, A, 1905 (Box Box 24)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0024
      - Subject 3134:The Streets of New York, 1905 (Box Box 25)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0025
      - Subject 3141:Raid on a Cock Fight, A, 1905 (Box Box 26)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0026
      - Subject 3206:Spanish Barbecue, 1906 (Box Box 27)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0027
      - Subject 3213:Old Swimming Hole, The, 1906 (Box Box 28)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0028
      - Subject 3215:Convict's Bride, The, 1906 (Box Box 29)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0029
      - Subject 3218:Weighing the Anchor, 1906 (Box Box 30)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0030
      - Subject 3223-B:Lone Highwayman, The, 1906 (Box Box 31)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0031
      - Subject 3241:Nelson-McGovern Prize Fight, 1906 (Box Box 32)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0032
      - Subject 3277:Colon to Panama Canal Picture, 1907 (Box Box 33)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0033
      - Subject 3278-A:If You Had a Wife Like This/How Would You Like a Wife Like This?, 1907 (Box Box 34)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0034
      - Subject 3278-C:If You Had a Wife Like This/How Would You Like a Wife Like This?, 1907 (Box Box 35)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0034A
      - Subject 3293:Gay Girl Playing Pool, 1907 (Box Box 36)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0035
      - Subject 3302-B:Opening Day, Jamestown Exposition, 1907 (Box Box 37)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0036
      - Subject 3306:Dear Little Sister, 1907 (Box Box 38)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0037
      - Subject 3310:Bigger than He Looked, 1907 (Box Box 39)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0038
      - Subject 3324:Tenement House Battle, A, 1907 (Box Box 40)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0039
      - Subject 3327:Finish of Scrappy Patsey, The, 1907 (Box Box 41)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0040
      - Subject 3348:Mags Jag, 1907 (Box Box 42)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0041
      - Subject 3355-A:Mr. Easy Mark, 1907 (Box Box 43)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0042
      - Subject 3355-B:Mr. Easy Mark, 1907 (Box Box 44)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0042A
      - Subject 3362:Light! Fight! White!, 1907 (Box Box 45)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0043
      - Subject 3366:Crooked Dog, 1907 (Box Box 46)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0044
      - Subject 3372:Waltzing Walker, 1907 (Box Box 47)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0045
      - Subject 3374-B:Yale Laundry, 1907 (Box Box 48)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0046
      - Subject 3374-C:Yale Laundry, 1907 (Box Box 49)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0046A
      - Subject 1337:Energizer, 1907 (Box Box 50)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0047
      - Subject X-247:Motion Pictures Patents Company Meeting, undated (Box Box 51)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0048
      - Subject G-319-B:False Alarm, A, 1905 (Box Box 52)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0049
      - Subject 7032:Her Morning Exercise, undated (Box Box 53)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0050
      - Subject 7037:Eve's Temptation, undated (Box Box 54)
        International Mutoscope Reel Company
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0051
      - Subject 7116:Love Conjuror, The, undated (Box Box 55)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0052
      - Subject 7134:After the Bath, undated (Box Box 56)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0053
      - Subject 7141:Call of Love, The, undated (Box Box 57)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0054
      - Subject 7148:Why Men Leave Home, undated (Box Box 58)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0055
      - Subject 7295:Stunning Wallop, A, undated (Box Box 59)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0056
      - Subject 7344:Ladies' Night in a Turkish Bath, undated (Box Box 60)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0057
      - Subject 7345:Her Morning Ablutions, undated (Box Box 61)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0058
      - Subject 7359:Interior Decorator, The, undated (Box Box 62)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0059
      - Subject 7567:Stolen Locomotive, The, undated (Box Box 63)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0060
      - Subject 7582:Saved by a Monkey Wrench, undated (Box Box 64)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0061
      - Subject 7583:Eve's Leaves, undated (Box Box 65)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0062
      - Subject 7587:Runaway Pullman Car, undated (Box Box 66)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0063
      - Subject 7598:In Dreamland, undated (Box Box 67)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0064
      - Subject 7599:Mexican Fandango, undated (Box Box 68)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0065
      - Subject 7662:Babes in the Woods, undated (Box Box 69)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0066
      - Subject 7688:Doctor's Office, The, undated (Box Box 70)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0067
      - Subject 7689:In the Cherry Orchard, undated (Box Box 71)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0068
      - Subject 7693:Pullman Up-to-Date, undated (Box Box 72)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0069
      - Subject 7705:Blonde Crazy, 1931 (Box Box 73)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0070
      - Subject G7351:Artist's Dream, The, undated (Box Box 74)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0071
      - Subject 7460:In the Nick of Time, undated (Box Box 75)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0072
      - Subject 7562:Chased by the Howling Redskins, undated (Box Box 76)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0073
      - [Unknown Subject number]:Shooting Up the Town, undated (Box Box 77)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0074
      - [Unknown Subject number]:Whispering Smith Rides, undated (Box Box 78)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0075
      - Subject 7366:Frontier Days, 1915 (Box Box 79)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0077
      - Subject 7369:Curse of Drink, The, 1915 (Box Box 80)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0076
      - Subject 7106:Her Daily Dozen, undated (Box Box 81)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0078
      - Subject 7634:Magic Parasol, The, undated (Box Box 82)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0079
      - [Unidentified Western Fragment], undated (Box Box 83)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0080
      - Subject 7335(?):Broadway Melody, The, undated (Box Box 84)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0081
      - Subject 7654:Electric Chair at Sing Sing, undated (Box Box 86)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0083
      - Subject 3370: [Girl $9.98], undated (Box Box 111)
        Accession No.: 1974:0223:0001
      - Subject 3355-A:Buys a Dog but Gets a "Lemon", undated (Box Box 114)
        Accession No.: 1981:1138:0001
    - Sub-subseries 2, Created, 1965; undated
      Sub-subseries consists of reels created by Crockwell and intended for viewing in a Mutoscope machine.
      - Crockwell Color Animation No. 1, undated (Box 85)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0082
      - Crockwell Color Wheel No. 1, undated (Box 87)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0084
      - Crockwell Color Animation No. 2, undated (Box 88)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0085
      - Crockwell Rose Spray-paint Reel, undated (Box 89)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0087
      - Crockwell Playboy and Dancer Reel, undated (Box 90)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0088
      - Crockwell Color Wheel No. 2, undated (Box 91)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0089
      - Crockwell Color Wheel No. 3 (1965) (Box 92)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0090
      - Duopusses, undated (Box 93)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0091
      - Crockwell Mixed Animation and Printed Card Sequence, undated (Box 94)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0092
      - Crockwell Color Wheel No. 4, undated (Box 95)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0093
      - Crockwell Color Wheel No. 5, undated (Box 96)
        Accession No.: 1974:0023:0094
  - Subseries 3, Flip Books, 1968; 1969; undated
    Subseries includes flip books created by Crockwell (who sometimes referred to them as "Thumb Books") and other artists. It is possible unbound larger cards in this subseries were intended to be mounted onto a Mutoscope reel and viewed via a Mutoscope machine. Due to their size these cards have been physically arranged and described along with the flip books. Boxes C364A and C364B are nested inside C364.
    - no title (Box C364a)
      - [Photographs from Crockwell's films], undated (Folder 1)
        Frame enlargements printed on Mutoscope cards.
      - [Unknown artist], undated (Folder 2)
      - [(Unfinished) Anne Ciccarelli], undated (Folder 3)
      - [Jane Fowler], undated (Folder 4)
        Cards 1-26
      - [Jane Fowler], undated (Folder 5)
        Cards 1-29
      - [Michelle Cherney], undated (Folder 6)
      - [Peep Stevens 3/26/68], 1968 (Folder 7)
      - ["A Modern Melodrama: Death by Smog or Overpopulation" Gibson -- Mutoscope II], undated (Folder 8)
      - [Dolly Witherspoon], 1969 (Folder 9)
      - [Unknown artist], undated (Folder 10)
      - [Carol Ann Holt], undated (Folder 11)
      - [Sherbrooke], 1968 (Folder 12)
      - [Sylvia Kaminski "The Kiss"], undated (Folder 13)
      - [Cecily Vaughan], undated (Folder 14)
        Cards 1-59
      - [Crockwell flip book materials], undated (Folder 15)
        "An Early Painted Sequence" (photographs); "A Late Short Sequence" (photographs); Color Wheel #3 Stencil; photo; "Houdini Unchained" flip book.
    - no title (Box C364b)
      - [Unknown artist], undated (Folder 1)
      - [Claudia Struthers], undated (Folder 2)
      - [Mock-Ups & Sketches for "Sun Rise" Thumbprint/Mutobook], undated (Folder 3)
      - [Unmounted Crockwell Mutoscope cards], 1967 (Folder 4)
      - [Unmounted Crockwell Mutoscope cards], 1967 (Folder 5)
      - [Unmounted Crockwell Mutoscope cards], 1967 (Folder 6)
      - [Unmounted Crockwell Mutoscope cards], 1967 (Folder 7)
      - [9 Thumbprint flip books], 1967
        8 titled Sun Rise, 1 untitled
    - no title (Drawer Poster Drawer 47)
      - [Two sheets of uncut Douglass Crockwell flip books], ca. 1967 (Folder 5)
        Uncut flip book cards from Sun Rise, and untitled flip books (see Box C364b for cut and assembled examples). Sheets originally misidentified as "Czech animation strips."
- Series 4, Technology
  Series includes Mutoscope machines, cameras and camera parts. For more information please contact the Curator of Technology at the George Eastman Museum, (585) 271-3361, ext. 369.